<?xml version="1.0"?>
<gameList>
	<game>
		<path>./Mario Kart 64.n64</path>
		<name>Mario Kart 64</name>
		<playcount>3</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20220308T023711</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Donkey Kong 64.n64</path>
		<name>Donkey Kong 64</name>
		<desc>K. Rool has ape-napped the Kongs!

Can Donkey Kong rescue his friends, reclaim the Golden Bananas and save his homeland from certain doom? Take out some Kremlings with Chunky's Pineapple Launcher or Lanky's Trombone. Float through the air using Tiny's Pony Tail Twirl. Even Rocket to the sky with Diddy's Jetbarrel!

-Don't forget the mini-games! Challenge a seal to a race around the lagoon, go on a crazy mine cart ride, and be on the lookout for a blast from the past...

-Four players can join in on super split-screen action or duke it out in a single-screen free-for-all!

-Use of the required Expansion Pak (included) allows incredible real-time lighting effects and massive environments.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/n64/Donkey Kong 64-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19991122T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rare, Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure, Puzzle, Platform</genre>
		<players>4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mario Party.n64</path>
		<name>Mario Party</name>
		<desc>Every game in the main series has a standard Party Mode in which up to four players play through a board, trying to collect as many stars as possible. In every turn, each player rolls a die and progresses on the board, which usually has branching paths. Coins are primarily earned by performing well in a minigame played at the end of each turn. On most boards, players earn stars by reaching a star space and purchasing a star for a certain amount of coins. The star space appears randomly on one of several pre-determined locations and moves every time a star is purchased, usually occupying a blue space.
Every Mario Party contains at least 50 to almost 110 minigames with a few different types. Four-player games are a free-for-all in which players compete individually. In 2-on-2 and 1-on-3 minigames, players compete as two groups, cooperating to win, even though they are still competing individually in the main game. Some minigames in Mario Party are 4-player co-op, even though it doesn't say it. In most situations, winners earn ten coins each.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/n64/Mario Party-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19990208T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Hudson Entertainment, Inc.</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure, Puzzle, Strategy, Family</genre>
		<players>4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Rayman 2.n64</path>
		<name>Rayman 2: The Great Escape</name>
		<desc>Rayman 2 takes place in a world called The Glade of Dreams. An army of Robot Pirates, led by Admiral Razorbeard, invades this world and destroys the Heart of the World, the world core. This greatly weakens the resistance's power and disables Rayman's powers, leading to his capture.

Globox, a friend of Rayman, is later also captured and put in the same cell as Rayman aboard the Pirates' prison ship. Globox restores one of his powers through a silver lum given to him by Ly, a fairy. Rayman escapes the prison ship, and is separated from Globox again. He learns that in order to stand a chance against the Pirates, he needs to find 4 ancient, magic masks to awaken Polokus, the spirit of the world.[10] He travels through the Glade of Dreams via the Hall of Doors, a magical place linked to various locations in the world, controlled by the ancient Teensies.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/n64/Rayman 2-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19991029T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Ubisoft</developer>
		<publisher>Ubisoft Entertainment</publisher>
		<genre>Platform</genre>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Super Smash Bros..n64</path>
		<name>Super Smash Bros.</name>
		<desc>It's a Bumpin', Bruisin', Brawlin' Bash!

The many worlds of Nintendo collide in the ultimate showdown of strength and skill! Up to four players can choose their favorite characters - complete with signature attacks - and go at it in Team Battles and Free-For-Alls. Or venture out on your own to conquer the 14 stages in single-player mode. Either way, Super Smash Bros. is a no-holds-barred action-fest that will keep you coming back for more!

-Plunge headlong into battle with your favorite Nintendo characters: Mario, Link, Donkey Kong, Pikachu, Samus, Yoshi, Kirby and Fox... plus 4 hidden characters!

-Characters use their own trademark attacks, such as Mario’s fireballs and Link’s sword.

-Grab a Fire Flower or Poké Ball and send your opponent sailing out of the arena.

-Compete in 8 different settings, each from a character’s home world and each with its own dangers.</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/n64/Super Smash Bros.-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19990426T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>HAL Laboratory</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Fighting, Platform, Party</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<playcount>3</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20220314T022724</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Mario Kart.n64</path>
		<name>Mario Kart 64</name>
		<desc>Three… Two… One… GO! The signal light changes and you drop the pedal to the metal. Take on up to three friends in the split-screen VS games, or race solo in the Mario GP. Tell your friends to bring it on in the highly competitive Battle mode. Advanced features allow you to race with your “Ghost”. The driving data from your best run appears as a transparent character on the screen. No longer must you simply race against the clock -- you can actually race against yourself!

-Save your hottest Ghost data to a portable N64 Controller Pak™ (Sold Separately)

-Collect multiple power-up items!

-Twenty different courses -- 4 Cups with 4 courses each and 4 special Battle mode courses!

-Everyone’s favorite characters are back and gorgeously rendered, including two new additions, Donkey Kong™ and Wario™!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/n64/Mario Kart-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19970210T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Racing</genre>
		<players>4</players>
		<playcount>1</playcount>
		<lastplayed>20220314T025153</lastplayed>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Diddy Kong Racing.n64</path>
		<name>Diddy Kong Racing</name>
		<desc>Timber the Tiger's parents picked a fine time to go on vacation. When they come back, they're going to be faced with an island trashed by the spiteful space bully Wizpig - unless the local animals can do something about it! So join Diddy Kong as he teams up with Timber the Tiger, Pipsy the Mouse and Taj the Genie in an epic racing adventure unlike anything you've ever experienced before!

-This unique game blends adventure and racing like no other game!

-Roam anywhere you want on the island by car, plane or hovercraft!

-An enormous amount of singe-player and multi-player modes!

-Feel the action when you use the N64™ Rumble Pak™ and save your times on the N64™ Controller Pak™!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/n64/Diddy Kong Racing-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19971124T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Rare, Ltd.</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure, Racing</genre>
		<players>4</players>
	</game>
	<game>
		<path>./Legend of Zelda, The - Ocarina of Time.n64</path>
		<name>The Legend of Zelda: Ocarina of Time</name>
		<desc>Ganondorf, the evil King of Thieves, is on the move, threatening the peaceful land of Hyrule.  He is determined to steal his way into the legendary Sacred Realm in hopes of harnessing the power of the mythical Triforce.  As the young hero Link, it is your destiny to thwart Ganondorf’s evil schemes.  Navi, your guardian fairy, will guide you as you venture through the many regions of Hyrule, from the volcanic caves of Death Mountain to the treacherous waters of Zora’s Domain.  Before you complete this epic quest, you’ll delve into deadly dungeons, collect weapons of great power and learn the spells you need to conquer the most irresistible force of all-time.

• The immersive storyline and environments draw players into an amazing 3D world.
• Time travel allows you to play as Link in different stages of his life.
• New gameplay features include a unique targeting system and 1st and 3rd person perspectives.
• Up to three games can be saved simultaneously to memory!</desc>
		<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/n64/Legend of Zelda, The - Ocarina of Time-image.jpg</image>
		<releasedate>19981123T000000</releasedate>
		<developer>Nintendo EAD</developer>
		<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
		<genre>Action, Adventure, Role-Playing, Puzzle, Platform</genre>
	</game>
</gameList>
